// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the most important factor for losing fat?",
    answer: "Caloric deficit",
    options: [
      "Caloric deficit",
      "Meal frequency",
      "Meal timing",
      "Carb intake"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who would have the hardest time achieving body recomposition (gaining muscle while losing fat)?",
    answer: "A lean, advanced trainee",
    options: [
      "Someone using anabolic steroids",
      "Some who is overweight/obese",
      "A lean, advanced trainee",
      "A new trainee"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following factors contributes the most to muscle growth?",
    answer: "Mechanical tension",
    options: [
        "Mechanical tension",
        "Metabolic stress",
        "Muscle damage",
        "Muscle confusion"        
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following describes the important “eccentric phase” on a bicep curl?",
    answer: "When you lower the weight back down",
    options: [
      "When you curl the weight up",
      "When you squeeze your biceps at the top",
      "When you lower the weight back down",
      "When you hold the weight at the bottom"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does RPE stand for?",
    answer: "Rating of Perceived Exertion",
    options: [
      "Rating of Potential Exertion",
      "Reps Possible to Exhaustion",
      "Rating of Perceived Exertion",
      "Rating of Perceived Exhaustion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Muscle soreness...",
    answer: "Can be a useful proxy that you hit the target muscle",
    options: [
      "Can be a useful proxy that you hit the target muscle",
      "Is very important for muscle growth",
      "Shouldn’t happen when training with good form",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Leneigh is a late-beginner/early-intermediate lifter who wants to build full-body strength and muscular size, with an emphasis on leg development. Assuming she does multiple exercises for multiple sets for her legs each workout, how many days per week should she train her glutes to leg gains without seriously risking recovery issues?",
    answer: "2-3x per week",
    options: [
      "1x per week",
      "2-3x per week",
      "5-7x per week",
      "No lifting, focus on cardio"      
    ]
},
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "For an average lifter using standard technique, which of the following muscles is least activated by the barbell back squat?",
    answer: "Hamstrings",
    options: [
      "Quadriceps",
      "Gluteals",
      "Hamstrings",
      "Adductors"         
    ]
},
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Roberto is an intermediate lifter who has been weight training for almost 4 years. He really wants to grow his chest. Assuming he is taking most sets close to failure, how many sets per week should he do to give him the best muscular gains without seriously risking recovery issues?",
    answer: "14 sets per week",
    options: [
      "4 sets per week",
      "14 sets per week",
      "24 sets per week",
      "34 sets per week"
    ]
},
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which is the most appropriate protein recommendation for an average lifter in a caloric surplus whose primary goal is to gain muscle?",
    answer: "1.6-2.2 g/kg bodyweight (0.7-1 g/lb)",
    options: [
      "0.8-1.2 g/kg bodyweight (0.35-0.55 g/lb)",
      "1.6-2.2 g/kg bodyweight (0.7-1 g/lb)",
      "2.8-3.4 g/kg bodyweight (1.3-1.5 g/lb)",
      "3.4-4 g/kg bodyweight (1.5-1.8g/lb)"
    ]
},
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "You’re programmed to do a max effort set of 4-6 reps on the deadlift. If you put on a lifting belt and use it properly, which of the following is least likely to occur?",
    answer: "You significantly decrease core activity",
    options: [
      "You lift more weight",
      "You lift the weight faster (more explosive force)",
      "You significantly decrease core activity",
      "You significantly increase IAP"    
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following activities has been shown to acutely reduce muscle protein synthesis?",
    answer: "Cold water immersion",
    options: [
      "Cold water immersion",
      "A high sugar meal",
      "Foam rolling",
      "Stretching between sets"      
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Rachael is an advanced-level lifter who has been training for both strength and size for almost 10 years. On an AMRAP set, roughly how many reps would you expect her to hit with 80% of her daily 1 rep max on the squat?",
    answer: "7-10 reps",
    options: [
      "4-6 reps",
      "7-10 reps",
      "12-15 reps",
      "16-20 reps"  
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which component of metabolism refers to activities like bringing in the groceries and is a major factor in metabolic adaptation to weight loss?",
    answer: "NEAT",
    options: [
      "NEAT",
      "TEF",
      "BMR",
      "EAT"  
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following would cause muscle protein synthesis to be elevated for the longest period of time?",
    answer: "1 hour of weight training",
    options: [
      "1 hour of weight training",
      "10g of whey protein",
      "20g of whey protein",
      "3g of leucine"  
    ]
},
];